superbikeplanet.com 2018-10-29

# Privacy Policy – SuperbikePlanet

We promise not to disclose your private information to any third party except if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Superbikeplanet.com users or the public. We take all reasonable care in handling your personal information to ensure its security both offline and online.

#### Types of Information We Collect:

You are free to browse superbikeplanet.com without submitting any personal information at all. Your IP address (your current Internet address) is stored in the server logs at the time of your visit, as it is on all web sites. We do not collect any personal information (such as a name, address or e-mail address) when you visit the site.

#### Cookies:

We use browser cookies to keep track of which stories you have read, and other information about your session. Cookies are small pieces of text that are stored on your hard drive between visits. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain any private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit or use the site and you can choose to refuse the cookies, delete the cookies from your hard drive or turn off cookies at any time by updating your user profile preferences via your internet browser software.

#### Postings on the Soup Classifieds:

Posting items for sale on the Soup Classifieds is free, but requires a name, telephone number and e-mail address.

Posting this information for others to view can be dangerous and if you are in the least bit concerned about this, you should not post any ads here. You should, instead, buy an ad in a paper-based media product where most of that information is required but no one ever bitches about the privacy policies of newspapers, etc. Such is life.

#### Sending us e-mail:

Occasionally, readers send us e-mail. Hence, their e-mail address may be stored in one of our computers. We don’t do anything with these e-mail addresses, other than to clean out our e-mail program’s address book occasionally and think silently Who in the hell is rotaxfever9@mindspring.net? Who are all these people in my address book? I don’t know 90% of them. Am I getting early Alzheimer’s?

We hate spammers just as much as you do and would maim people who gave away or sold our e-mail address. We don’t do it.
